Are you suffering from the Fargo curse?
Why even bother showing up at events
anymore, right? Fargo has it all worked
out for you anyways. More often than
ever, I'm hearing these comments. He's a
much higher Fargo. I have no chance.
She's a much lower Fargo. I'm supposed
to win easily. And now there's even
score predictions of how matches should
go between certain Fargo numbers. That's
totally insane. It's like the future's
already been written for us and players
are buying into this. It's creating huge
expectations and therefore pressure and
a lot of frustration since when does a
number behind somebody's name determine
how a match is going to go. Look, it's
not the best player that's going to win.
It's the player that plays the best.
You're playing the table and you're
using your opponent as fuel to kick you
into a higher gear. Break free from this
chain and take responsibility for your
own focus and the things that matter.
Play the game and not the stats. Good
luck.